Hao Wu

User Experience Designer

haowu.design/ hermia.haow@gmail.com 416-871-3063 linkedin.com/in/hermia-wu/ github.com/hermiawu

PROFILE

I am a passionate designer, who is excited to be beginning a career in UX.

Being keen on studying human behaviours, I have spent about 5 years researching how humans access the physical space and how they deal with numbers, especially financial behaviors. When it comes to the digital world, HCI is the field where I would ideally like to work in. I would love to use my interdisciplinary skills of architectural design and financial research to create digital solutions that are not only charmful but also going to make users' life better.

SKILLS

Sketching/Wireframing/Protot yping (Figma, Sketch, Invision, POP App, Principle, Protopie) Graphic Design (Adobe Suite: Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign, Premiere, After Effects), Design Systems, Storyboards, User Experience Mapping, Java, Javascript, HTML, CSS, jQuery, Project Management (Trello, Asana, JIRA), Agile

EXPERIENCE

Graphic/UI Designer | Self-Employed

MAR 2020 - PRESENT, TORONTO, ON

- Redesigned UI from inception to final product and successfully launched brand new McMaster Sumobot Competition website (<u>sumobot.ca</u>) which increased visitors by 50%
- Developed high-quality mock-ups and UI for 2 mobile apps

Junior Architectural Designer | Oleson Worland Architects

DEC 2019 - PRESENT, TORONTO, ON

- Implemented innovative conceptual design sketches, and models for review by design software, like Adobe Suite and AutoCAD
- Established and maintained collaborative relationships with involved parties, including City Hall, clients, other designers and engineers
- Refined company's workflow, which increased the efficiency by 30%

EDUCATION

BrainStation | Diploma, User Experience Design

AUG - OCT 2020, TORONTO, ON

University of Toronto | Bachelor of Arts, Architectural Studies

SEP 2016 - 2019, TORONTO, ON

Daniels Undergraduate Technology Award. Graduate with High Distinction. Dean's List Scholar

Southwestern University of Finance and Economics | Bachelor of Economics, Investment

SEP 2013 - 2017, CHENGDU, CHINA

Graduate with High Distinction. Meritorious Award in The Mathematical Contest in Modeling 2015

PROJECTS

Hm.So.. - Home Social App | Lead UX Designer, Researcher

AUG 2020 - PRESENT, HACKATHON (HACK THE 6IX)

- Home-based social app that mainly helps people express themselves properly to improve their relationship with roommates
- Coordinated the project and collaborated with developers to realize text to emoji transformation (NLP), public space management, and activity status animation within 36 hrs

<u>Pre.Module</u> - Prefabricated Building App | Full-Stack UX Designer

SEP 2020 - PRESENT, BrainStation Capstone

- To educate and encourage young professionals to access prefabricated buildings in order to reduce their rental financial pressure
- Took the role of a whole-process UX designer, creating this case study from research, to ideation and realization, and to the stage of multi-platform marketing